-(waves crashing)
-(machinery whirring)
(ominous music playing)
(eerie music playing)
(hammering continues)
(woman gasping softly)
(ominous music playing)
(gasping and panting)
(gentle soulful music playing)
(whispers) Wait, wait.
(Copley on radio) We've got at least
16 guards on site, four vehicles primed.
Konrad's moving guns.
Lots of them.
(Copley) He's a real piece of work.
He's up to his ears
in scanners and other jamming technology,
so we're gonna lose comms
the moment we're inside.
Question. Do we ever get any days off?
-You're such a millennial, Nile.
-(Nile) Hey, it's a fair question.
Nile, we didn't have any days off
when we were the new ones.
(Andy) All right, Joe, Nicky,
you guys take the hedge maze.
(whispers) What?
-(laughing)
-(Nicky) Really?
(Andy) Don't worry.
-It's not going to be like 1853.
-(Nile) What are you guys talking about?
There was a cannon.
We didn't see it.
(Nicky) It was Booker.
His head was blown clean off by a cannon.
We couldn't find it in the maze.
And he couldn't help, for obvious reasons.
(both laughing)
(Nile) You think he's okay?
(mysterious music playing)
Let's do this, guys.
(Copley) Let us know
if you put eyes on Konrad.
(Nile) Two guards have moved
to the waterfront.
No sign of the big man yet.
(sighs deeply)
-(Copley) Hey.
-(gasps)
(dramatic music playing)
-(Andy) He's only got one weapon.
-You sure?
Do I need to remind you
you're not immortal?
Fair enough.
-(thug groans)
-(bones crunch)
(groans)
(both laugh)
All right, guys. You know what to do.
(on radio) Get as many guards
to chase you as you can.
("Make It Look Easy"
by Gin Wigmore playing)
♪ I make it look good ♪
♪ I make it look easy… ♪
(gun firing loudly)
-(Joe) This one is mine!
-(Nicky) No, no, no!
-(laughs)
-♪ I make it look good ♪
♪ Last name, Danger ♪
-(guards clamoring)
-(machine gun firing)
♪ Got a dead man on my back… ♪
(Nile) It worked.
They're heading your way.
(speaking Italian)
They're supposed to follow us,
not to catch us.
(engine revving)
(gunfire)
♪ I make it look easy… ♪
All right. We're heading in.
♪ Easy ♪
♪ I make it look good ♪
(laughs)
-♪ I make it look good ♪
-(song ends)
(Andy) What? No sex swing?
You must have seen some bad art
in your time, haven't you?
(Andy) This bad?
Not in at least a century.
Weapons being loaded.
They're on the move.
Commotion must've spooked 'em.
(bullet ricochets)
(tense music playing)
(grunting)
I need to remind you,
you're not immortal either.
-Shall I?
-Nope. I always go first.
(grunting)
(Joe) Nicky.
Slow down, Joe! Slow down!
(chuckles)
(tires squealing)
(Joe) Let's give these guys a run.
(Nile) Ah shit!
Fuck!
(dramatic music playing)
(man groaning)
(groans)
(both grunting)
(man yells)
(Nile) Konrad's upstairs.
Get in! Get in! Get in!
(dramatic music continues)
(yells)
Nicolò.
(biker yells)
-You okay?
-Yeah.
(pulsing dramatic music playing)
(tense music playing)
(gun fires)
-(Andy) Move.
-(Nile) Stay on my six.
(Nile) Sixteen guards, huh?
(Andy) Go easy.
CIA never taught him how to count.
Can we just, you know, do this?
(dramatic music playing)
(body thuds)
Looks good on you.
("Edamame" by bbno$,
feat. Rich Brian playing)
(Andy sighs)
(Copley) We're all set.
My CIA contact will be here
in seven minutes.
He'll make sure the weapons are collected.
Okay, let's start walking.
♪ Whoa! I'm a big bag hunter
With the bow ♪
♪ She got a big bad dumper, drop it low ♪
♪ Mama called me
And she happy with the grow ♪
♪ Never ever fold for a thottie
That's an oath ♪
-(laughter in background)
-(man) Shh!
You gonna call it?
-I'm thinking.
-(Joe) She has tells.
Took me centuries to learn them.
She has tells.
(speaking Italian)
-No one can read Andy.
-No, I think I can.
-Yeah.
-(all laughing)
-Yeah?
-(Copley) Oh yeah.
(men shushing)
She's telling the truth.
(all laughing)
-(Joe) Last two rounds.
-Her left eye twitched last two rounds.
(all laughing)
The left eye.
What?
-Bullshit.
-You sure?
Bullshit.
(men shushing)
(all groaning)
-Thank you.
-(laughs)
You know the worst part
about being mortal?
Just the fucking hangovers.
(all laughing)
-(Andy) Too brutal, man. I don't know.
-(cell phone vibrating)
-(Nile) What the--
-I don't know how you do it.
-Be right back.
-(all sighing)
Whoo! The drinking is fun.
-Who you texting?
-It's my new boyfriend.
Come on. Let's go to bed.
(both speaking Italian)
(in Italian) Sure, have another glass.
You'll snore all night like a boar.
(in English) Wow.
(Nicky in Italian) You sleep talk
all night.
-(Joe) Ciao.
-(Nicky in English) Good night.
(Nile sighs)
You did real good today.
Even though I drove a boat
halfway into the villa?
Hey, listen, sometimes quick
is better than subtle.
Oh! Today's lesson?
-Yes, it is.
-(chuckles)
You know, you joke a lot, but…
how are you doing?
Me?
I'm really happy.
I'm at peace.
Didn't look peaceful when you were
throwing that guy out the window.
It wasn't supposed to be.
(both laugh)
Send it now.
I mean, I'm mortal. I'm not retired.
My contact confirmed
that Konrad wasn't the buyer.
Just a conduit,
like the others last month.
So who is? And what are they doing
with all that artillery?
The real buyer is elusive.
Leaves almost no trace.
This CCTV photo
is all they're able to get me.
Hey.
What?
-You know this woman?
-(Nile) Yeah.
(ominous music playing)
(hesitates) I mean no. No, I…
I think I recognize her.
I've dreamt about her.
I didn't think it meant anything.
It wasn't clear.
(Andy) Okay, just…
tell me exactly what you saw.
(Nile) This woman.
She's, um…
She's in a room,
an ancient room, surrounded by books.
(female voice whispering)
She's here, isn't she?
(whispering voice continues)
(Nile) And there's someone else there. A…
A man, but…
(Nile sighs)
…I can't see his face.
But the books, I think they're his.
(female voice echoing indistinctly)
None of you had a choice.
(Nile) She's hurting him.
And then…
(Andy) And then what?
(Nile) And then I wake up.
Think it means something?
I don't know.
There's not enough data yet
to get facial recognition,
but the moment they do, I'll let you know.
Great. Thanks, Copley.
(footsteps retreating)
(Nile sighs)
-Hey. Don't worry about this, okay?
-(pats leg)
We'll figure it out.
(horns honking)
-(glass shatters)
-(man cursing in French)
Booker.
It's nice to finally meet you.
(mysterious music playing)
I've been waiting for a very long time.
(Booker) Quynh?
(Quynh) So…
how do I find Andromache?
-(dull thud)
-(tense music playing)
(man groaning)
(mellow rock music playing)
So, do you have any idea where we can go?
I was thinking of having some time alone.
(Nicky) Huh.
Just a little time for myself.
Okay.
Thanks.
(Andy speaking Italian)
You're coming with me.
I am?
I need your help.
(speaking Italian)
Try and have some fun without me.
-(Joe laughs)
-(Nicky) Bye, boss.
Nile.
(Nicky speaking Italian)
Don't worry, okay?
Enjoy yourself.
("Alcolicixbenzina" by Ibisco playing)
(Nile) What's up with Joe?
Did something happen after the wreck?
He said he wanted some time alone.
You're not okay with that?
I know this man a thousand years.
I know when he's lying.
(Joe speaking Italian)
-Thank you.
-We're following him.
What?
Come on.
(seagulls cawing)
(Quynh sighs deeply)
Again, do you know where Andromache is?
It doesn't matter if I do.
I'm in exile.
-But you can find her.
-Are you listening to what I say?
I'm exiled.
How'd you find me?
You made it easy.
Staggering around Paris drunk for months.
(Booker scoffs)
(Quynh) It's a miracle
you weren't discovered.
(Booker chuckles)
So you bringing me here is…
is you doing me a favor, right?
(laughs) Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm telling you the truth.
I'm out of it.
You wanna know where Andy is?
This is not the way to do it.
He will need clean clothes.
(grunts)
Has she spoken of me?
She never stopped.
(somber music playing)
All that time,
with every last breath I took,
I imagined she was trapped somewhere
in the same hell as me.
All I wanted
was to get out and release her from it.
Just to find out
she'd been free for 500 years.
She was living in her own kind of hell.
Now, that's hard to believe.
("Fils de Joie" by Stromae playing)
(Joe speaking French)
Merci.
Not much of an exile
if you're dropping in
to deliver groceries.
Booker's alone.
Nicky, caro, what…
-He's alone.
-Yeah.
And you were the one
screaming for his head.
(in Italian) We abandoned him.
(in English) He made his choice, Joe,
when he shot Andy and betrayed all of us.
Guys, something's happened. He's not here.
There's blood on the wall,
blood on the floors.
When is the last time you talked to him?
-Joe.
-No reason in pretending now, Joe.
I don't know. A week… a week ago.
(sighs) He was fine… I don't--
We gotta tell Andy,
but it keeps going to voicemail.
Come on. We'll meet them at Echo.
-Nicky. Nicky!
-(Nicky) Come on. Come on.
(Copley) All this way, and you still
haven't told me who it is we're meeting.
I made a promise the last time I saw him
that I would protect his secret.
It's just around this corner here.
Actually, I think maybe
I should just check in with him first.
-Yeah.
-(Andy) See if this is okay.
Of course. I'll be on call.
Okay.
(Copley sighs)
(mysterious music playing)
(laughs softly) Andromache.
You were expecting me?
Let's just say I'm not surprised.
Thank you.
(man) You're still wearing
Quynh's necklace.
Do you still dream about everyone?
I keep tabs.
-(Andy) Do you know about Nile?
-Nile Freeman.
I do.
Well, she's been dreaming about a woman.
A woman who was here with you.
I thought maybe you'd know something.
Why don't you come to the library?
I think we should talk.
So do I.
You know, Tuah, I almost completely
stopped believing in our purpose
until a friend of mine discovered
a ripple effect.
Where's this friend?
(Copley) So, uh,
how old are you, then?
Let's just say 2,300 for a round number.
You?
I'm 43. (chuckles)
Impressive.
(rumbling)
(unsettling music playing)
(Copley) Uh… (sighs)
This is…
all about immortals?
(Tuah) Yes, our place in history.
The facts and fictions
that have found their way
into the writings of cultures
and civilizations… the world over.
Evidence of what you found out
within 43 short years.
Cause and effect.
A life saved in Ghana…
Leads to a Nobel Prize in medicine
three generations later.
What happened over there?
(Tuah) Those volumes were stolen
by one of us.
The woman Nile's been dreaming about?
I've written books
on every single immortal.
You, your friends, the work that they--
Who is she, Tuah?
She's gone by many names over the years.
She goes by Discord now.
Sounds ominous.
(Tuah) As it should.
She was the first of our kind
that I had met.
A long time ago.
(Copley) How long?
She is older than any of us.
She is the first of the immortals.
No.
No, Andromache is the first.
What are you saying?
I… I… I found no trace of anyone earlier.
-By design.
-What do you mean, "by design"?
There was a time
where we walked together peacefully.
But over the centuries,
we saw how fear of those who are different
can turn even good men cruel.
(dramatic music)
(Quynh screaming)
(crowd shouting and jeering)
We have to do something.
They're like us.
(Quynh) Please! No! No!
(screaming)
(crowd continues shouting)
(Quynh screams)
Such evil cannot be unseen.
-(crowd jeering)
-(Quynh screaming)
(Quynh screaming) No! No! No!
Quynh!
(yelling) Quynh!
That was the day you saved me.
She was there too?
Yes.
Afterwards, I retreated
to my books, my research.
And Discord retreated too.
Then she spent the next five centuries
amassing untold wealth and power
so as not to fear enemy or attack.
Dealing arms with people like Konrad.
What does she want from us, Tuah?
(Tuah) I don't know.
She's not the same person
that I once knew.
And now that she knows your histories,
your relationships,
I believe that all of you
could be in danger.
It's been millennia
since I've been afraid.
But I am scared of what she is capable of,
and so should you.
Tuah.
Do you think there's a chance
she might know
that I've lost my immortality?
How long has it been?
Around six months.
(sighs shakily)
Andromache.
I think you should pack a bag.
I already have.
(Joe scoffs) Because I knew
what you were gonna say.
(in Italian) No.
You thought you knew what I'd say.
(in English) You lied to us.
(Nile) They're back.
-(Andy) Hey.
-(Nile) Hey.
Who's this?
This is Tuah, an old friend of mine.
"An old friend"?
You knew there was another,
and you never told us?
Boss, you lied to us?
I didn't lie. I--
A lie of omission is still a lie.
In Andromache's defense,
I asked her not to tell anyone of me.
Something's happened to Booker.
What?
-Did you go see him?
-It's not like that.
Yusuf went to see him.
They've been talking the entire time.
-(Nile) We went to his place in Paris.
-(Nicky) Blood everywhere.
Discord.
Possibly.
-(intriguing music playing)
-(Copley) What else do we know about her?
I mean, where she lives, her…
her habits, her MO.
(cell phone vibrating)
(speaking French)
It's Booker.
Don't worry, boss. We got this.
(Joe) We have to.
(ominous music playing)
(music fades)
Thanks for coming.
-Joe.
-(Joe) Hey.
-What happened?
-(Booker) Hmm.
I need to see Andy.
(door opens)
(softly) Andy.
She's out.
What?
Quynh.
She couldn't find you, so she found me.
(mysterious music playing)
(Quynh) Andromache.
I have returned to a world
darker than the tomb I finally escaped,
only to learn
you have gone on living in it freely
all these centuries.
I need to hear the words
that will free me from my true prison.
That of a broken promise.
You and me.
Until the end.
(Quynh) Find me where you always could.
I have to go meet her.
-Andy, don't.
-It's Quynh.
-(Booker) Give her space, Nile.
-(door opens)
Andy, she could have reached out to you
in a million ways.
Instead, she kidnaps Booker
and does all this for face time?
That seem sane to you?
For 1,500 years, it was just her and me.
What do you know about her, Nile?
I know you can die and I can't.
And I know your head's not on straight
when it comes to her.
So tell me, if our places were swapped,
would you let me go alone?
(engine starts)
(Booker) So I guess you must be, uh,
Tuah, right?
It's good to meet you finally, Sébastien.
-Do you mind if I call you Booker?
-Whichever you like.
How long are you guys gonna keep this up?
This whole cold shoulder bit. Hmm?
How do we know
you haven't sold us out again, Book?
(tuts) Come on.
Well, I, uh…
I guess you don't.
-(tense music playing)
-(panting)
(screaming in distance)
(coins jangling)
(tense music building)
-(yelling)
-(both grunting)
(screams)
(echoing screams)
(screaming continues)
(gasping)
(grunting)
(Quynh) Andromache.
This is not who you are.
(panting)
(man coughing and gasping)
Woke up alone in the car.
Thought you ditched me.
(water running)
Thought about it.
Anything I can do?
Can you give me back five centuries?
Wish I could.
What if she doesn't recognize me?
I don't mean physically, but…
who I've become.
What if I don't recognize her?
(Nile) Andy,
I've never seen you like this.
I've been like this for hundreds of years.
(church bells tolling)
I'll be right behind you.
Okay.
(pensive music playing)
Excuse me,
can I use this phone for a second?
(woman) Of course.
(men speaking Italian)
(Joe laughing)
(emotional music playing)
I don't know how to…
There are no words
to explain how I failed you.
Can you imagine it?
Trapped
in the dark.
Every muscle
screaming for air.
My life returning just long enough…
to remember,
to hope.
I'm so sorry.
How long have you been back?
Months.
Why didn't you come find me sooner?
You couldn't even find me
in one small area of ocean.
I searched.
I did. I searched for centuries--
(Quynh) But you stopped.
Quynh.
Look at me.
You once told me…
the only thing you fear is being alone.
The way it was
before we found each other, Andromache.
-I am alone.
-(Andy) You're not.
You have me.
You have Joe and Nicky.
Quynh.
Come home.
You can join us.
You're asking me to join you
and your endless war?
Huh?
Fight beside you?
Fight for mortals, the ones who drowned me
in a coffin at the bottom of the sea?
You have no idea
what has happened.
I can't…
I can't leave them.
I'm not…
What?
Looks like you have made your decision.
Don't.
Quynh, wait.
(tense music playing)
Stay back.
(music fades)
Quynh.
(grunts)
("Hate or Glory" by Gesaffelstein playing)
Wait. I don't wanna fight.
(panting)
I remember the woman
I gave that necklace to a long time ago.
And you're not her.
("Hate or Glory" continues playing)
(knife clatters)
Shit! Andy.
Hey!
(Nile) Shut it down.
Discord's here.
Nile! No, no, no.
That's Nile?
(Andy) What do you know about Nile?
Discord.
That's how you got out?
You're with Discord.
("Hate or Glory" continues playing)
Stop!
Stop.
(in Vietnamese) I curse you
for all your lifetimes!
("Hate or Glory" continues playing)
(song fades)
(in English) Clever. Hiding in a church.
But you can't stay here forever.
I didn't think we'd be meeting so soon.
I was there, you know.
I can still remember it.
The acrid stench of hate in the air.
Tell me, Nile Freeman,
how does a good Christian girl like you
stomach what Andromache's doing?
Playing God with mankind.
We're not playing God.
We're helping. We're doing what's right.
Did it feel right
leaving your family behind?
Letting them think you were dead?
That's what she made you do, isn't it?
That was my decision, my choice.
(Discord) None of you had a choice.
Not with her.
Andromache's obsession
with interfering with human affairs
is the reason we're hunted.
You will make your friends stop
or I will.
You are the last immortal.
There will be none born after you.
And you have a power
you can't even imagine yet.
One day you'll understand.
You and I are going to end
immortal interference together.
I'm not doing anything with you.
We're connected.
Do you have a birthmark on your left arm?
The first immortal
and the last.
I'll see you soon, Nile.
(ominous music playing)
(music fades)
(Copley) Clearly
Discord has the ability to find us.
But now we have
all the surveillance footage from Rome.
Next time Discord or Quynh
walks past a camera,
we'll know where they are.
-(Joe) Well, that's something.
-What does it mean?
"I'm the last."
(Tuah) Discord knows
something about you we don't,
and we need to figure it out.
So what do we do about Quynh?
I don't know.
(pensive music playing)
(groans softly)
(exhales deeply)
(Tuah muttering indistinctly)
(Tuah) Booker.
(Booker) Are you working on something?
Always.
(laughs softly)
Tell me something.
At any point,
has Nile ever wounded Andy?
Yeah. When they first met, they fought.
Uh, Nile stabbed Andy.
Why?
Well, I, uh…
I have a theory that that is the reason
why Andy has lost her immortality.
What are you talking about?
Any day, any one of us
could wake up mortal, right?
Nothing that lives… lives forever.
There was a legend
that Discord and I had heard of
centuries ago.
It tells
that a wound from the last immortal
has the power to take away
anyone else's immortality.
So Nile is the reason Andy's mortal?
(Tuah) Hmm.
Well, I believe
that Discord is going to use Nile
to try to kill all of us.
But there's more.
The legend also states
that the wounded immortal
may bestow the gift of immortality
to another before it is lost.
A transfer.
(Tuah) Precisely.
But it has to be willingly given.
So Andy could… become immortal again?
If one of us become mortal, yes.
But again,
it's just a theory.
(Booker) Andy?
Can I talk to you for a sec?
(Andy) Sure.
I just wanted to tell you,
after all of this is over,
I'll probably go.
Don't be stupid, Book. We need you.
We never should have left you behind.
You did what you had to do.
I deserved it.
Sit down.
You remember the moment you left me?
You told me to have faith.
Right?
Well, the thing is, I, uh…
I didn't,
and it wrecked me.
Seeing you walk away,
thinking I'd never see you again…
was, uh… (laughs softly)
(laughs) But life is funny
'cause here I am talking to you.
I'm really grateful for that.
We've known each other too long.
Yeah, so many things I left unsaid
all the time.
(sighs deeply)
When you get to do things
over and over again,
forever, without expiration date, that's…
that's where you forget
to say things to one another.
(reflective music playing)
I'd love an expiration date.
You know why?
'Cause it gives meaning.
What I mean is,
maybe this is the perfect time
for Quynh to be back.
You wish for something
for so long…
but it's just not that simple.
She's betraying you out of hurt.
It's not over yet.
We always make it through.
Have a little faith, Andy.
And get some sleep.
(Discord) She let you down again.
I'm sorry.
I pulled you from the ocean
because I needed you by my side.
You may have lost Andromache,
but you don't have to be alone.
How can I help you, Quynh?
I want them to suffer.
Andromache and the others, they will.
No.
Everyone.
That I can help you with.
(menacing music playing)
(suspenseful music playing)
(horns honking, people shouting)
(guard speaking Mandarin)
(brakes hiss)
-(tense music playing)
-(guards clamoring)
(engine revving)
(man shouting in Mandarin)
(guards speaking Mandarin)
(Quynh gasping softly)
(bones crack)
(bones continue cracking)
Drop your weapons.
(workers screaming)
(workers clamoring)
(guard yells)
(Booker) Show me what you got.
Really?
-Why not?
-(Nile chuckles)
(Booker) I might be
a couple of hundred years old,
but I can still teach you a thing or two.
(Nile) Oh, you're gonna
teach me something? All right.
Okay, Book.
(chuckles)
Hey, Tuah.
You're just in time to watch me
school this old man.
-Go easy on me. It's been a while.
-(Nile) Mm-hmm.
(Tuah) Perhaps you're not ready
for this, Booker.
(Nile) All right.
(swords slashing)
(Nile chuckles softly)
How am I doing, Tuah?
You're a natural.
I would like a chance too.
-Nah, let me play a little.
-(Nile chuckles)
I insist.
All right.
(ominous music playing)
(rhythmic music playing)
(Tuah chuckles)
(music building)
-(Booker groans)
-(Nile) Shit.
(Booker) Argh!
Sorry, Book.
(groans) No, it's all right.
(groaning) That was fun.
(Booker panting)
I'm gonna take care of this.
All right.
I'll be back.
(Booker groans)
(Tuah) You shouldn't have done that.
I told you it was just a theory.
Only a theory.
(Booker) I can already tell.
It's… it's not healing.
Then we don't have much time left.
Remember, it must be given willingly.
Tuah, you understand
Andy can't know about this.
She can't.
Promise me.
(computer beeps)
(footsteps approaching)
(Copley) They're just outside Jakarta.
We need to get everyone together
in the library.
(Booker) I'll be right there.
(Andy) You do something stupid again?
(Booker) Yeah, well, you know me.
As usual.
Copley wants us to meet downstairs.
All right.
(emotional music playing)
(water running)
You okay?
(Booker) Yeah. (chuckles softly)
It's just been a while, you know.
It's not for me.
(Andy) Meet you downstairs.
The nuclear facility is a black site.
Privately owned by the Chinese
on Indonesian soil.
It's not meant to exist.
The confusion could be helpful.
Yes.
This is the security footage
that my contacts were able to obtain
before all outside contact was cut off.
(tense music playing)
(Copley) We have to assume
that her black ops team
has full control of the system,
from the control room
to the coolant chamber.
Now, look at the large structure here.
It's the core.
It appears that, inside here,
they've, uh,
planted a device.
We should assume that
it could create an explosion that would…
breach the facility.
And irradiate the entire area.
Ten million people.
(Copley) They've planted shaped charges
capable of incapacitating any one of you
for an extended
and vulnerable period of time.
(Nile) It's a trap.
Discord is using the bomb like bait.
She knows we'll try to stop her,
and we're playing right into her hands.
That's exactly what she told me.
She wants us.
All of us.
Whatever their motives are,
a bomb is a bomb.
And both of them are willing to blow it
to get what they want.
We don't have a choice.
We have to go.
Gear up.
(Andy) Thanks.
(both chuckling softly)
Do you remember that game we used to play
in Ireland at the Cliffs of Moher?
(Nicky) Yeah.
Running towards the edge?
-(laughs)
-See who chickens out first?
You never gave up.
No.
(in Italian) Talk to me.
(in English) I can't shake
this fear, Nicky.
And what are you afraid of?
We could end.
(sighs)
You know, Andromache,
she walks 3,000 years alone
before she found Quynh.
But me and you,
we were together from the start.
I can't look at us
and believe it is arbitrary.
Things end.
What I feel when I see you,
when I see your heart…
that's truly immortal.
(somber music playing)
(epic music playing)
(Copley on radio) It would be ill-advised
to discharge any firearm
in the vicinity of the core.
(Andy) James, negative contact.
Yeah, that means
you'll meet resistance further in.
(on radio) Remember, we have to assume
they have our positions at all times.
(tense music playing)
Okay, doors on the south side.
Through them, up the stairs.
Stay along the wall and you're
in the upper levels of the reactor.
Any movement?
-Still nothing.
-(Copley) Joe, anything on your side?
(Joe) Negative contact on this side too.
Shaped charge.
(Copley) Expect additional
small explosives throughout the compound.
Maybe they're not stupid enough
to stay in a nuclear facility,
now that they've set a bomb to blow it up.
(indistinct radio chatter)
(Nile) Okay, they wanna go hand-to-hand.
Remember, there's always an asshole.
(wires whirring)
-(men shouting)
-(Andy) Go, go, go! Move!
(dramatic music playing)
-(loud explosion)
-(yelling)
(Joe) Nicky, get up!
(knife whizzes)
(dramatic music building)
(Copley) Get to the control room.
Open that door.
(Nicky) Copley, which way do we go?
All right. Okay.
Down the hall, through the corridor.
It'll wrap around to the control room.
(gun firing)
I found the asshole.
-(electricity crackling)
-(grunts)
-(groans)
-(Nile) Andy!
Nile!
(shouts) Nile?
(Copley) If I can get into their system,
I can lead you to the bomb.
We haven't much time.
(door beeping)
-(sighs) The system has a firewall.
-(Copley) Look for a manual override.
There's no manual override, Copley.
(twig snapping)
This was her plan all along.
Discord wants to separate us.
(tense music playing)
(grunts)
(gunfire continues on radio)
(Andy on radio) Copley?
(screaming)
(alarm blaring)
(alarm stops)
(Andy on radio) Tuah? Nicky? Joe?
Nile.
(grunts)
(Andy) We're blocked.
(Booker) This way.
Joe, Nicky, Nile!
(Andy) They're gone, Book.
Discord is watching us.
(Booker) Let's go.
(keypad beeps, door chimes)
She's controlling the doors.
She's trying to split us up.
Book, when this door opens,
you have to go first.
No, no, no. You go first.
They're gonna slaughter me
if I go out there.
You always go first.
I'm not joking.
Me neither, Andy.
What?
-I gave it to you.
-How?
Stay behind me.
(Andy yells)
(Andy panting)
(Booker) I got my expiration date.
You have a purpose.
This is mine.
(Andy) Book!
(muffled) No! Book!
(emotional music playing)
(yelling)
(emotional music building)
No!
(Booker yells)
(muffled yelling)
-(knife slices)
-(Booker grunting)
(yells, groans)
-Book!
-(Booker groaning)
(Booker panting)
(muffled) Book, I…
(groaning)
Sébastien.
(breathing slows and stops)
(muffled yelling)
(grunting)
(yelling)
(broken glass crunching)
(grunts, panting)
(ominous music playing)
You're alone.
Give me the bomb, Quynh.
Just go with Discord.
Give her what she wants.
She wants us dead.
You stood with Andy for centuries.
Centuries.
How could you betray her like this?
(dramatic music playing)
You know nothing about me and Andy.
(both grunting)
(Quynh) What…
(panting)
I'm not…
(breathing shakily)
I'm not healing.
Quynh…
(Quynh) What have you done to me?
(Nile) I didn't…
I'm sorry.
(Discord) Shh.
It's okay.
(Quynh moans)
(Nile gasps)
(sword clatters)
(indistinct radio chatter)
(tense music building)
Nile! Joe!
Nicky!
Tuah!
(ticking)
Is this where you tell me
that this isn't who I am?
I used to think it was my job to save you.
But in the end,
each one of us has to decide for ourselves
who we really are.
(ticking continues)
(ticking stops)
(helicopter whirring in distance)
(Andy) Where is she taking them, Quynh?
Where?
I don't know.
(groans)
(tense music playing)
(Discord) Bags loaded. Let's go!
(engine whining)
(Andy groans)
(yells)
-(alarm blaring)
-(window smashes)
(Andy groans)
(alarm blaring)
Circle around!
(dramatic music playing)
(Discord panting)
Your hand isn't healing.
You're mortal.
This had nothing to do
with immortal interference, did it?
(Discord) Don't look at me like that.
Do you know what it's like
to wake up after an eternity
and find yourself suddenly mortal?
Every minute
is a step towards death.
Time means nothing
until it means everything.
if you give it no meaning.
Your friends don't have
much time left, Andromache.
(scoffs)
That's your plan?
You're gonna kill them?
(Discord) No.
Nile will.
She's a destroyer.
She can take their immortality…
and give it to me.
She'll never hurt them.
You think I'm gonna give her a choice?
You think your life means more
than one of theirs?
To me, it does.
I suspect the first few won't be willing.
And then again,
torture goes a long way.
I will come for them!
And when you do,
the playing field will be level.
(groaning)
(dramatic music building)
(music fades)
(emotional music playing)
There's a lot… I hate about this century,
but this
I like.
(chuckles softly)
I never knew Discord was mortal.
I'm gonna find them.
The only question is…
are you gonna do what you do best
and fight by my side?
No.
(ominous music playing)
You will fight by my side.
-Where do you think you're going?
-I always go first.
Not anymore, you don't.
Try and keep up.
-(Quynh) Oh yeah?
-(Andy) Yep.
(rhythmic music building)
("Roll The Credits"
by Danielle Ponder playing)
♪ I could feel it
I won't come down ♪
♪ Found myself above the sky ♪
♪ Tell my mama, tell my daddy ♪
♪ That love is falling from the sky ♪
♪ La, la, la-la, la-la ♪
(vocalizing)
(vocalizing continues)
(rhythmic music playing)
(emotional orchestral music playing)
(ominous orchestral music playing)
(dynamic rhythmic music playing)
(emotional orchestral music playing)